"Kissing at High Tide"
Yeah
Extend the contract by one month
One month?
You never let anyone stay for more than a day
It was just one night before
This time it was a month
Could it be...
Are you really attracted to him?
Don't regret it in the future
It's not too late to let go now
Jae Hoon
Minwoo is right
You…
I will never give my sincerity to anyone.
You only feel excited because you are bored
Ambiguity is like a lighter that you replace every day
You've always been so calm
You can handle it
But
Why is it different this time?
Why do I get shaken when I see Haejun?
The way Haejun eats bread
the way he smiles
always comes to my mind
Jae Hoon
You are a calm and rational person in business.
Why are you interested in college?
You broke all the rules
please
Jae Hoon
The heartbeat of this moment
You'll end up hurting yourself
please
Don't sink
Hello Kim Haejun
you look at me
What on earth have you been doing lately?
Don't answer the phone
Text messages not read
what happened
What kind of union can make people like this?
Just...
Teach your children to draw near home
What are you doing?
Now comes the interesting part
quiet
speak with mouth
crazy
You're pretty good at using your mouth.
a punishment
two
three
four
the last button
It's punishment time
use my rules
I am the master
You are the one who obeys
Eat
Sorry, I'm going to be late for school
If you don't go now, you will be read by the professor.
I'll find you again tonight
I'm leaving first. I'm sorry.
He will definitely run back right away
Just like a habit
©2025 SEEKMedia All Rights Reserved